{
    "success": true,
    "title": "Questions",
    "data": [
        {
            "id": 404,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "In phase 2 trial the response rate of Eltrombopag 70% and Placebo 11 % for ITP patients.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:02:37.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 405,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "Brigatinib is an irreversible dual inhibitor of anaplastic lymphoma kinase (ALK) and epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR).",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:02:54.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 406,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "The safety and effectiveness of Crizotinib have been established in pediatric patients with ROS1+ mNSCLC.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:03:24.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 407,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "Diarrhea is the most common adverse effect of Cazar FCT.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:03:46.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 408,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "First-line TASSO cut the risk of progression or death by 54% vs EGFR TKI comparator (erlotinib or geÔ¨Åtinib).",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:04:01.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 409,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "Cancer cachexia is not an alarming condition for cancer patient.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:04:20.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 410,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "TMZ is indicated in lung cancer.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:04:37.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 411,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "Ribociclib + ET is preferred by NCCN category 1.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:05:29.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 412,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "Tasso can be recommended in severe hepatic impairment patients.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:05:53.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 413,
            "quiz_id": 63,
            "question": "60mg OD without food is the recommended dose of Cazar FCT for HCC.",
            "option_1": "True",
            "option_2": "False",
            "option_3": "",
            "option_4": "",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-07-09T08:06:16.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        }
    ]
}